ABOUT ME

While working as a Customer Success Manager, I worked alongside the development team of an all-in-one benefits administration and HR software company.

I wanted to learn how to directly make changes and improve websites myself. This lead to my enrollment in a bootcamp at NSS.

PROJECTS

BookMark'D

- BookMark'd is a React app that serves as a way for users to organize the bookmarks of things they read online.
- Users can sort by what they are reading now, have finished, or want to read.
- This app utilizes React, Reactstrap, and CSS

Backend Capstone

Python

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Reactstrap
- JavaScript, React
- Python, Django, SQL
- Git and JSON

CONTACT INFORMATION



502-216-0346



rsnasraty@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/rsnasraty/



https://github.com/rsnasraty

ROXANNE NASRATY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Vanderbilt University

BACHELOR OF ARTS - BA, PSYCHOLOGY

• Completed in August 2016

Nashville Software School

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

- Intensive full-time software development bootcamp anchoring learning with both individual and team-based projects.
- Tech Stack: Python/Django; Javascript; React.js; HTML;CSS3; SQL fundamentals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Client Success Manager

BERNARD HEALTH | MAY 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

- Bernard Health is a benefits brokerage and manufacturer of the insurance benefit management software, "BerniePortal":
- Managed multiple client accounts and partnered with clients to plan, process, and implement getting employees enrolled in insurance benefits via BerniePortal.

Outbound Marketing Team Member

BERNARD HEALTH | JANUARY 2019 - MAY 2019

- Scheduled product demos and discovery calls for account executives over the phone and via email.
- Maintained, updated, and organized prospect and client records in Zoho

Medical Office Administrator

HOSPITAL INTERNAL MEDICINE ASSOCIATES | NOVEMBER 2017 - JANUARY 2019

- Hospital Internal Medicine Associates, is a private medical practice.
- Managed all clerical duties including patient data entry, calendar management, scheduling, human resources, and travel coordination.